别紧张
It's okay.
放松
Relax.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我只是花些时间研究你而已
I'm just gonna learn about you for a little while.
可以吗？
Is that okay?
我就叫你凯若兰吧
I'm gonna name you Kerolien
以我同学名字命名
after my friend at school.
她真的超级棒
She's really nice.
但她有时会在课堂上放屁，然后假装自己没放
But she farts in class sometimes and pretends like she didn't.
你可不要这样呀，
So, please don't do that,
不是只有你在玻璃罐里，
'cause you're sharing this jar now,
如果你臭臭的，别人就不会喜欢你了好吧？
and the others won't like you if you smell. Okay?
你好呀
Hi there.
我不住在这附近，
I'm not from around here,
但我想着结交一些新朋友
but I was hoping to make some new friends.
我能和你说会儿话吗？
Can I talk to you for a little bit?
我……不和陌生人讲话
I... I don't talk to strangers.
确实是这样
Of course you don't.
确实不该你很聪明呀
You shouldn't. You're smart.
但我是来和你交朋友的，
But I'm here to be your friend,
真希望我俩能马上熟络起来
so, hopefully, we won't be strangers for too long.
你叫什么？
What's your name?
文玲
Wenling.
叫我文也行
But everyone calls me Wen.
很高兴认识你，文
Well, it's nice to meet you, Wen.
我叫莱纳德
My name's Leonard.
我看你在捉蚱蜢呀
I see you're catching grasshoppers.
要我帮帮你吗？
Can I help you?
呃，行吧
Um, I guess so.
我小时候也特爱抓蚱蜢
I loved catching grasshoppers when I was your age.
-哇，你很厉害呀 -谢谢夸奖，文
- Oh, you're really good. - Thanks, Wen.
能麻烦把罐子递给我吗？
Can you pass me the jar there, please?
慢慢来
Wait.
先稳一下罐子里的蚱蜢们
Let the ones inside calm down a bit.
可不能吓到他们
We don't want them to panic.
进去喽
There you go.
你是天生就会,
Are you just a natural,
还是说有人教你怎么抓蚱蜢的？
or did someone teach you how to catch grasshoppers?
艾瑞克爸爸教我的
Daddy Eric taught me.
我正在研究他们
I'm studying them.
我长大后要去从事动物保护相关的工作
I'm gonna take care of animals when I grow up.
你叫你的爸爸还带名字的？
You call your dad by his first name?
这样他俩就能知道我在和谁说了呀
It's so they know who I'm talking to.
两个爸爸，艾瑞克和安德鲁爸爸
There's Daddy Eric and Daddy Andrew.
学校里的其他孩子都只有一个爸爸
All the other kids at school only have one dad.
所有迪士尼的节目里也都只出现一个爸爸
All the Disney Channel shows only have one dad, too.
你对此感到困扰吗？
Well, does that bother you?
并没有
No.
除了我指导老师不停地说
Except when my guidance counselor keeps saying
有两个爸爸是多么棒的时候
how it's so great that I have two dads.
反而让我感觉
For some reason, it makes me feel like
她像是在说反话
she's saying the opposite.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
没
Nothing.
没事
Nothing at all.
你几岁了，文？
How old are you, Wen?
再过六天就八岁了
I'll be eight in six days.
那就提前祝你生日快乐啦
Well, happy almost-birthday.
说来也巧，
In fact, it just so happens
我刚好有东西送你
that I have something for you.
我看到它时，就在想说这花真漂亮
I saw it, and I thought it was pretty,
我就把它摘下来了
so I decided to keep it.
把它作为生日礼物提前送给你
So, consider it an early birthday present.
要是你不喜欢，
And if you don't like it,
我们也可以用它来玩游戏
we can play a game with it instead.
什么游戏？
What kind of game?
我们轮流摘花瓣，然后问对方问题，
We'll take turns pulling petals off and asking questions,
等把花瓣摘完，我们就能更加了解对方了
and by the time we're done, we'll know each other better.
-成为更好的朋友 -嗯，好吧
- Be better friends. - Hmm, 'kay.
你最喜欢的电影是什么？
What's your favorite movie?
魔女宅急便
Kiki's Delivery Service.
我还没看过这部
I haven't seen that.
我会去看看的
I'll check it out.
好了，该你了
Okay, your turn.
你为什么会来这儿？
Why are you here?
莱纳德？
Leonard?
我在这里的原因？
Why am I here?
嗯,我来这里是来与你交朋友的
Well, I suppose I'm here to make friends with you
还有你的爸爸们
and your dads.
或者再抓些蚱蜢
Maybe catch some more grasshoppers.
你嘴唇上怎么会有个小小的伤疤？
How'd you get that tiny little scar on your lip?
对不起，文
I'm so sorry, Wen.
我是在不该问的
I shouldn't have asked that.
哪怕是对这个游戏来说，也问得太私人了
It's... It's too personal, even for this game.
没关系
It's okay.
我出生时是兔唇
My lip was broken when I was born.
爸爸们说请了许多医生才修复好
My dads said it took a lot of doctors to fix it.
我没像你这样的伤疤,
Well, I don't have a scar like you,
但如果你能深入我的内心观察，
but if you could look inside,
你便会感受到我心已碎
you'd see that my heart is broken.
为什么心碎？
Why is it broken?
源于今天我不得不做的事
Because of what I have to do today.
你不得不做什么？
What do you have to do?
那些人是你的朋友吗？
Are they your friends?
你是我的朋友，文
You're my friend, Wen.
无论发生什么，我都希望你能记得这点
No matter what happens, I want you to remember that.
过来的那几人更像是我的同事，而非朋友
The others who are coming are more like people I work with.
我们四人有一项极其重要的任务要完成
You see, the four of us have a very important job to do.
可以说这可能是历史长河中最最重要的任务
In fact, it might be the most important job in the history of the world.
文，这不是针对你
This isn't about you, Wen.
或者你的爸爸们
Or your dads.
好吗？
Okay?
你们毫无过错，但我恐怕你们仨
You haven't done anything wrong, but I'm afraid the three of you
需要作出艰难的抉择
are gonna have to make some tough decisions.
可怖的抉择
Terrible decisions.
而我以我的破碎之心期求你不必遭受如此
And I wish with all my broken heart that you didn't have to.
文！
Wen!
你的爸爸们不会让我们进去的
Your dads won't want to let us in.
你得告诉他们必须这样做
You have to tell them they must.
否则我们只能自寻入口了
Otherwise, we're gonna have to find our own way in.
你明白吗？
Do you understand?
文，告诉我你清楚了！
Wen, tell me you understand!
♪ 噫
♪ Oh
- ♪ 妙哉妙哉，爱也……
- ♪ Love is always better...
-还不赖 -奶酪味道不错哦
- This isn't bad. - The cheese is good.
是吧？事实证明你看她来了
See? Factual proof. There she is.
你不需要时刻管着她
You didn't need to check on her.
你们得马上回屋里去
You have to come inside right now.
有一些陌生人，他们想闯进来，
There's strangers, and they want to come in,
-并且他们很吓人！ -哇哦，慢些说
- and they're scary! - Whoa, whoa, slow down.
-快点！快点！ -好的，好的，我来了
- Hurry, now! - Okay, okay, I'm coming.
-我们回屋去 -知道了，我的天
- We're coming inside. - God, okay.
-快点！ -宝贝，发生什么了？
- Come on! - Honey, what's happening?
-告诉我们怎么急…… -放松一些，没事的
- Tell me what's so... - Relax, relax. Okay. It's okay.
-没事的 -文，出什么事了？
- It's okay. - Wen, what's up?
文，文，没事的跟我说，宝贝，发生什么事了？
Wen, Wen, it's okay. Listen, sweetie. What happened?
你在害怕什么?
What scared you?
他们，有四个人
There... there were four of them.
有个大块头，他叫莱纳德
The big one, his name's Leonard.
他说我们必须要帮助他们
He... he says we have to help them.
他说他们有有史以来最为重要的任务要完成
He says they have the most important job in the history of the world.
耶和华见证人?
Jehovah's Witnesses?
棒极了
Great.
他们身上带了武器
They have these weapons.
你好
Hello in there.
我叫莱纳德，
My name is Leonard,
还有几个我的同事跟我在这里
and I'm here with some associates of mine.
能麻烦开一下门吗?
Can you open the door, please?
这家伙块头TM超大
This guy is frigging huge.
我们该怎么办？
What do we do?
我不知道呃……
I don't know. Um...
好声好气地劝他们离开？
tell them to go away nicely?
嗨，你好，莱纳德我们……
Hi. Uh, hello, Leonard. We...
是安德鲁爸爸还是艾瑞克爸爸?
Is that Daddy Andrew or Daddy Eric?
我已经见过你们可爱的女儿——文了
I met your delightful daughter Wen already.
她心地善良，善解人意你们肯定感到非常自豪
She's so thoughtful and kind. You two should be very proud.
我是艾瑞克
This is Eric.
有什么我们可以帮忙的吗?
Is there something we can help you with?
有的
There is.
要不先开门吧？
Why don't you open the door?
面对面谈话能更好交流
It'll be easier if we speak face-to-face.
让他们快走开
Tell them to go away.
拜托，快赶他们走
Please make them go away.
文，安静
Wen, please.
呃，我们并不想招待访客
Uh, we weren't expecting visitors.
听上去有些粗鲁，但是我们确实不想被人打扰
I don't want to sound rude, but we'd like to be left alone.
我理解
I understand.
我很抱歉在你们的假期打扰你,
And I'm sorry to intrude on your vacation,
尤其是在如此美丽的风景胜地
especially in such a beautiful place as this.
快赶他们走！
Make them go away!
文
Wen.
其实，这对我们来说也不容易
You should know that this isn't easy for us, either.
我们从没来过这湖
None of us have been to this lake before.
而且我们四人，也从未设想过
And the four of us, we never thought
我们会站在此处和两位良善聊天
we'd be here talking to you nice people.
还有哪些人在那里？
Who else is out there with you?
还有塞布丽娜、艾德利安和雷蒙德
I'm here with Sabrina, Adriane and Redmond.
总共我们四个
And the four of us are here
试图挽救大众而聚在此地
because we're trying to save a whole bunch of people.
艾瑞克，快来，快来
Eric, come here. Come here.
但要达成此事，就需要你们的帮助
But we need your help to do that.
否则，我们将不成一事，
We can't do anything without you,
然而，隔门对话
and speaking through a door
只会让我们的行动难上加难
is making a difficult conversation near impossible.
什么？
What?
有个女人手握着
There's a woman carrying something
看上去连着锁链的，
that looks like a pick with a chain
链尾还带着锤头的镐
and a mallet head at the end.
我要报警了
I'm calling the police now.
不对吧没有拨号音
This can't be right. There's no dial tone.
什么？
What?
我们刚到这儿时我还检查过
I checked it when we got here.
是电池没电了吗？
Is the battery dead?
有电，但是无法拨号
The battery's not dead. It's not dialing.
正如我言，我们之间需要对话
Like I said, we need to talk.
无可奈何
We don't have a choice.
没错，你们也让我们别无选择！
Yeah, well, we don't have a choice, either!
只好报警了！
We're calling the cops!
嘿，我们知道你们没法报警
Hey, um, we know you can't do that.
手机信号都不在服务区内
None of our phones get service out here, either.
不好意思，我们还剪了你们的电话线
And sorry, we had to cut the phone line.
文文快给我手机
Wen. Wen. Wen. We-Wen, give me the phone.
我们并不想催促你们，
We don't mean to rush you,
只是时间已有些紧迫
but we're a little pressed for time.
请打开门扉，好让我们能够真正的交流
Please open the door so we can have a real conversation.
如果你们只是想对话，那为什么你们…… -嘘，文
If you want to talk, then why do you... -Shh. -Wen, Wen.
……还要带上那些吓人的武器？ -嘘，文，安静
...have those scary weapons with you? -Shh, shh. Wen. Wen.
它们不是武器，文
They're not weapons, Wen.
只是工具而已
They're tools.
- 赶紧把这破门打开！
- Just open the goddamn door!
我们有的是方法进来
We're coming in either way.
你们敢！我带着枪！
The hell you are! I have a gun!
你带过来了？
You brought it here?
说是也不是它在我们车后备箱的保险盒里
Yes and no. It's in the safe in the back of the truck.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
那就让我们看看你携带的枪，安德鲁爸爸！
Show us what you're packing, Daddy Andrew!
Show-and-Tell：说话课（展示并介绍课），国外小学通过展示并介绍自己喜欢的东西，从而满足学生的表现欲望与锻炼学生的演讲才能
我们都爱《说话课》
We all like show-and-tell.
只会在我拿枪指着你们脑袋时才会看到，
You'll see it when I'm pointing it at your head,
你们这群人渣！
you piece of crap!
你怎么回事？真是帮倒忙
What's wrong with you? You're not helping.
-你在惹恼他 -那又怎样？
- You're upsetting him. - What?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
雷蒙德、包括我们所有人都很焦虑和过激
Redmond is as anxious and passionate as we all are.
最后通牒，赶紧开门
I'm giving you one last chance to open the door.
他们想闯进来!
They're breaking in!
安德鲁，沙发！
Andrew, couch!
干得好，文继续
Good job, Wen. Keep going.
推过去
Push it.
好了
Okay.
安德鲁爸爸！
Daddy Andrew!
有我在，宝贝
I got you, baby.
他们进地下室了
They're in the basement.
一个在后门，一个在地下室
One is in the back, one is downstairs.
我们一起逃到车那边去
Let's make a run for it to the car.
我已经拿了钥匙了
I've got the keys.
没有必要弄得如此难堪
It doesn't have to be like this.
带着文逃出去
Get Wen out of here.
艾瑞克！
Eric!
我来救治他
Let me help him.
-等等…… -不要碰他！
- Wait... - Don't touch him!
我是护士！他受伤了！
I'm a nurse! He's hurt!
停下来！住手！
Stop! Stop.
艾瑞克
Eric.
艾瑞克爸爸
Daddy Eric.
拜托快起来我们要离开这里，爸爸
Please get up. We have to go, Daddy.
艾瑞克，快醒醒
Eric, wake up.
醒醒，艾瑞克！
Wake up, Eric!
嘘
Shh.
嘘，没事的
Shh, you'll be okay.
安德鲁，够了
Andrew, that's enough.
♪ 轻描兮
♪ To illustrate
♪  我了遗言
♪ My last remark
♪ 鲸内约拿，舟中诺亚 ♪
♪ Jonah in the whale, Noah in the ark ♪
♪ 晓谕之，彼何为兮……
♪ Tell me, what did they do...
我喜欢你的冰箱
I like your fridge.
谢谢，妈
Thanks, Mom.
♪ 君不见，吾辈须
♪ Man, they said we got to
♪ 积～积极兮 ♪
♪ Ac-cent-tchu-ate the positive ♪
♪ 消～消极兮  ♪
♪ And e-lim-i-nate the negative ♪
♪ 深信不疑 ♪
♪ And hang on to that affirmative ♪
♪ 然勿乱于，勿乱于…… ♪
♪ But don't mess, don't mess with... ♪
开车七小时，见面三刻钟
They drove for seven hours and stayed 45 minutes.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我在指望什么呢
What do you expect?
我妈问我时用的就是这句话
That's my mom asking how it's going.
你大可告诉她你错了
Well, you can tell her you were wrong.
安德鲁
Andrew.
永远在一起
Always together.
- 嗨
- Hi.
谢谢，小奶油
Thanks, Custard.
这是一笔非常重要的纸杯蛋糕订单
This is a very important cupcake order.
这样是不是会好受些
Let me see if this helps.
怎么样？
Is that better?
还是先不要动了
Try not to move.
快好了
Almost done.
我明天前
I have to finish
就得完成这笔特殊的订单
this special order before tomorrow.
一定咕噜咕噜圆满达成
It needs to be purr-fect.
能把电视声音调低吗?
Can you turn that down?
其实我们已经调低过一次，
We did when you asked before,
但我会调一下
but I'll do it again.
艾瑞克的伤口清理好了吗？
Is Eric cleaned up?
伤口是清理好了,但脑震荡很严重
He's cleaned up, yeah, but severely concussed.
嘿，艾瑞克
Hey, Eric.
你有感觉好些吗？
You feeling any better?
我……我很抱歉
I'm... I'm so sorry.
我之前从没看过这个动画，竟然意外喜欢
I've never watched this show before, but-but I like it.
那些人物，呃，很奇妙
The characters, um, they seem curious and good.
我能感受到它在探索和教导同理心
I get the sense that it explores or teaches empathy
和宽容心，实在是太可爱了
and tolerance, and that's just lovely.
同理心和宽容心？
Empathy and tolerance?
要在被你们捆绑的酷儿面前高谈阔论这些？
Is that what you're here to talk about now that you have the queers tied up?
哎
Oh.
安德鲁，我向你保证我们来此地
Andrew, I assure you that we're not here
内心不带有一丝仇视与偏见一点也没有
with hate or prejudice in our hearts. Not at all.
从头到脚找不出一道恐同的痕迹
We don't have one homophobic bone in our bodies.
我谁也不仇视
I don't hate anybody.
不过这扇破门我倒是挺讨厌的
I do have conflicted feelings about this door.
我们说的都是真的
You have to believe that.
在来此之前，我们根本不知道你们是同性伴侣
But we had no idea you were a single-sex couple until we got here.
这点真是意想不到
That one was a surprise.
我想既然你能发誓,那我一定会"信"你
Well, I guess if you promise, then I have to believe you.
我是说我们和你们一样，普普通通
I mean, we're normal people just like you.
- 我们别无选择 -凡事总有选择！
- We have no choice. - There's always a choice!
他说得挺对
He's right about that.
定夺铸就命运
Our choices make our destiny.
差点把这句话纹身上
I almost got that tattooed.
好吧，你说得对，安德鲁
Okay, you're right, Andrew.
凡事总有选择
There's always a choice.
我们选择来此地
So we choose to be here.
请问大家能聚过来吗？
Can everyone come in here, please?
差不多时间了
It's almost time.
到时做什么？
Time for what?
你们不用把我们绑起来
You don't need us tied up.
之前你们说是来对话的，那我们就谈谈
You said you were here to talk, so we'll talk.
嗨，艾瑞克，文……
Hi, Eric, Wen...
……还有安德鲁
...and Andrew.
我是塞布丽娜
My name is Sabrina.
我住在南加利福尼亚
I live in Southern California.
我住在一个你们可能从未听闻的镇子上
I live in a town you've probably never heard of.
我担任术后护士快五年了
I have been a post-op nurse for almost five years.
我花费了几乎所有的积蓄
I used most of my savings
来到宾夕法尼亚州，
to come out to Pennsylvania,
来到此处，和你们交谈
to come here to talk with you guys.
我还有一个同父异母的妹妹在家中……
I have a little half sister back home...
……文，你多少让我想起了她
...and, Wen, you kind of remind me of her.
我想你们应该已经知道
Well, I think you-you guys already know
我的名字是莱纳德了
my name is Leonard.
然后，呃，
And, uh,
我很擅长捉蚱蜢，是吧，文？
I'm good at catching grasshoppers, right, Wen?
我来自芝加哥
I'm from Chicago.
我是一名二年级教师，
I'm a second grade teacher,
并且我也负责组织课后辅导项目
and I run the after-school program.
我同时还是一名调酒师我……
I'm also a bartender. I...
好了该我了吧？
Okay. Me?
我是下一个吧？
Am I next?
你们好
Hi there.
我是雷蒙德,我喜欢在沙滩上散步,
I'm Redmond, and I like long walks on the beach,
- 我还喜欢喝啤酒 - 嘿
- and I like beer. - Hey.
我们已经讨论过了吧
We already discussed this.
他们应当知晓我们都是谁
They deserve to know who we are.
等他们觉醒就是在浪费时间
We wasted time for this guy to wake up.
你知道吗，这种"认识你"的把戏毫无意义
You know, this get-to-know-you stuff doesn't matter at all.
改变不了我们或他们的将行之事
Doesn't change what we have to do or what they have to do.
当你脱口而出那些话语，你再听听自己说的，
When you say stuff like that, you sound how you sound,
依你，我们就不断恐吓，那会让他们
okay, you just scare them, you make it less likely
愈发不会相信我们并拒绝合作了
that they'll believe us or cooperate.
好吧，好吧，那我继续
Okay, okay, my turn it is.
我住在马萨诸塞州的梅德福那边
I live in Medford, Massachusetts.
在燃气公司工作,
I work for the gas company,
确保屋宅与公寓不会因燃气爆炸
making sure houses and apartments don't blow up.
我目前单身，简直难以置信
I'm single, if you can believe that.
我堕落过一段时间，如他们所说
I've done some time, as they say.
当我还懵懂无知时，呃……
Did a lot of, uh...
做了许多头脑发昏的坏事
questionable stuff when I was young and stupid.
但我现在已经洗心革面
But I'm much better now.
我父亲常常把我打得屁滚尿流，
And my father used to beat the shit out of me,
就像安德鲁刚干的那样
like Andrew just did.
真希望我能回到过去,
Wish I could go back in time,
让孩童的我拿起这玩意儿
give the kid-me this thing.
轮到我说了吧？
May I speak now?
希望我听上去不像个奇葩
I hope I don't sound confusing.
稍等，稍等一下
Hold on, hold on a second.
我们知道你们应该是某个团体的
We get that you guys are a part of some group
从你们的话语中，透露出，似乎你们想要……
and it sounds like, it sounds like you want to...
解决什么问题
fix things.
提供什么帮助
To help.
艾瑞克，你无须和他们多言……
Eric, you don't have to try to talk...
不不，没事，我就是想说出来
I... No, no, I'm okay. I want to say this.
如果你们想要招募我们，
If you're try... trying to recruit us,
那为什么还有人
I mean, why else bother
会对自我介绍感到烦扰，是吧？
introducing yourselves to us, right?
如果你们是想要改变我们的身心，
If you're trying to change us or make us different,
那你们所做的一切……
all of this...
只能说南辕北辙
this isn't the way.
有人能帮忙把后门的窗帘拉上吗？
Can someone put the curtain on the back door?
艾瑞克这是怎么了？
What's wrong with Eric?
当你处于脑震荡时，
When you have a concussion,
就会极度畏光
you're extremely sensitive to light.
好吧，对此我们也是爱莫能助
Well, there-there's nothing we can do about that now.
只能在避光的房间或我们弄暗客厅，
Well, he's only gonna get better if he rests
他才能感觉舒服些
in a darkened room or if we make it dark in here.
在我们提出提议前，不该转移他
We shouldn't move him until we make our proposal.
他可能需要在避光的房间里呆上数天，
He might need to be in a darkened room for days,
- 不光只是几小时- 你们不能把我
- not just a few hours. - You're not separating me
与安德鲁和文分隔
from Andrew and Wen.
我去看看能不能修好窗帘
I'll see what I can do with the curtains.
好了，其他暂且不论
So, whatever.
我，呃，我是艾德利安
I'm, um, I'm Adriane.
没错，我做过很多类型的工作，但是现在，
Yeah, I-I've been a lot of things, but-but right now,
或者说，呃，我来这儿之前，我是一名流水线厨师，
or, um, before I got up here, I-I was a line cook
就在杜邦圈的一家墨西哥餐馆上班
at a Mexican restaurant in-in Dupont Circle, D.C.
我超爱做菜
I love to feed people.
食物在我眼里不仅仅只是食用价值
It feels like it's more than food to me.
呃，天呐，还有什么可说？
Um, God, what else?
嗯……
Uh...
对了，我还养了两只猫咪
Oh, I have, um, I have two cats.
你一定会喜欢他们的，文
And you'd love them, Wen.
他们分别叫丽芙和拉夫
Their names are Riff and Raff.
你喜欢猫咪吗，文？
Do you like cats, Wen?
不要回应她，宝贝
You don't have to answer her, sweetie.
抱歉，文
Sorry, Wen.
电视我等会儿再打开吧，好吧？
Maybe I'll put it back on later, okay?
别管窗帘了
Forget the curtains.
时辰已到
It's time.
我们四人来到此地，是为了阻止末日来临
The four of us are here to prevent the apocalypse.
我们，当我说"我们"时，是指这屋内的每一位——
We-- and when I say "we," I mean everyone in this cabin--
都可阻止它发生，但须在你们的帮助下
can stop it from happening, but only with your help.
最终，世界是否终结
Ultimately, whether the world ends or not
完全取决于三位
is completely up to you three.
我看你是在发神经
You are having a psychological break of some kind.
你们家必须选择自愿献祭
Your family must choose to willingly sacrifice
三选一
one of the three of you
以阻止末日
in order to prevent the apocalypse.
在做完以我之见无比艰难的决定后，
After you make what I know is an impossible decision,
你们接着必须杀死那位献祭者
you must then kill the one you choose.
如果你们无法抉择，
If you fail to choose,
又或者你们无法执行献祭的那一步，
or if you fail to follow through with the sacrifice,
世界便会终结
the world will end.
你们仨会活下来，
You three will live,
然而其余人类，
but the rest of humanity,
70多亿人……
seven billion plus...
将化作烟尘
will perish.
他们疯了
They're lunatics.
而你们都将活得长久
And you will all live long enough
足以见证万物消亡的恐怖
to witness the horror of the end of everything.
而你们将遗留在这世界尽头，茕茕独立
And you will be left to wander the devastated planet alone.
永久淹没在……孤寂的浪潮中
Permanently and cosmically... alone.
莱纳德
Leonard.
我们没做错什么过
We haven't done anything wrong.
全然同意，你们没有
I agree with you. You haven't.
你们没有任何过错，然而却需承受如此之重
You haven't done anything wrong to... to deserve this burden.
你们家只是此次被选中决定我们命运的人而已
You're just the family chosen to decide for us in this time.
听我说，我们并不是来伤害你们的
Look, we're not here to hurt you.
如果我们真想那样，早就用上强力胶布了
If we wanted to hurt you, we would've used duct tape
- 而不是绳索 - 你别说话
- instead of ropes. - You stop.
你们必须明白我们无法
You have to understand that we cannot
也不会帮你们选择谁应当去献祭
and will not choose who has to be sacrificed for you.
还有，我们不能帮你们执行献祭
And just as importantly, we cannot act for you.
以及你们不能自杀
And you cannot kill yourselves.
我们不会选择任何人
We're not choosing anyone.
我们也不会牺牲任何人
We're not sacrificing anyone.
决不动摇
Not now, not ever.
即使这意味着世界上其他所有人的死亡?
Even if it means the death of everyone else in the world?
是的，即使我相信世界岌岌可危，
Yes. Even if I believe the world was at stake,
虽然我不信，但就是这么坚决
which I don't, that's what it means.
我将目睹世界沦灭千百遍
I would watch the world die a hundred times over
- 也不愿…… -天呐
- before having to... - Christ.
浪费时间
Waste of time.
他们绝对不会做出选择的
They're never gonna choose to do this.
但我也不会责难他们
And I don't blame them.
- 谁会去选…… - 闭嘴吧，雷蒙德
- Who would ever choose... - Shut up, Redmond.
你别想你所想，说你所说了
You just vomit everything you think.
哦，上帝，我们完蛋了
Oh, God, we are so screwed.
好吧，
Okay,
你们还需要听听这部分内容
you need to listen to this part, too.
我清楚地了解将会发生什么
I've been shown exactly what will happen
如果你们选择不进行献祭
if you choose not to make a sacrifice.
我们都预见了
We've all been shown.
预知的景象纷至沓来，我们无法阻止
We couldn't stop drawing the visions we saw.
我本以为我自己出了什么问题，
I actually thought something was wrong with me,
但那些景象实在是过于清晰，
but the visions were so strong,
过于具体，过于真实
so specific and so, so real.
塞布丽娜，艾德利安和雷蒙德，他们也都一样
Sabrina, Adriane and Redmond, they had the visions, too.
因此，它让我们聚在了一起，然后……
So, that led us to each other and...
它指引我们来到此处这间小屋
and that led us here to this exact cabin.
我们无从知晓我们被选中的原因
We have no idea why we were picked.
首先，城市会淹没
First, the cities will drown.
海洋会隆起滔天巨浪，仿若灭世巨拳
The oceans will swell and rise up into a great fist
重击所有建筑物和被困住的人们
and pound all the buildings and people into the sand,
连根拔起一切，卷入海中
and drag everything out to sea.
你们四个是真的有病，
There is something wrong with you,
如果连这都会信
with all of you, if you believe this.
紧接着一场可怕的瘟疫会降临
Then a terrible plague will descend
人们会发烧无力，
and people will writhe with fever,
肺里充满粘液
and mucus will fill their lungs.
这是病，精神病
This is psychotic.
这全是妄想
It's delusional.
你们寻求过帮助吗？
Did you try to get help?
放我们走，然后我们会帮你们
Let us go and we'll get you help.
天幕坠沉，冲撞地面
The skies will fall and crash to the earth
犹如玻璃碴
like pieces of glass.
上帝之指将焚焦地面
And God's fingers will scorch the earth
永夜将至，之于人类，光明永逝
and an everlasting darkness will descend over humanity.
你需要帮助！
You need help!
一切都会发生
This is going to happen.
我们也预见到只有你们的献祭方能阻止一切
And we've been shown that only your sacrifice can stop it.
来自谁的预兆？
Shown by who?
通过什么方式？
By what?
你能回答吗？
Are you gonna answer that?
你跟那些遍布城市角落的
You sound like every fake doomsdayer
虚假末日预言家别无二般
on every corner of every city.
来吧，跟我们讲讲
Come on, talk to us.
梦境可以有多种解读
Dreams can have many different meanings.
我们在你们的幻象中似乎有些模糊
Our part in your visions is kind of vague.
甚至感觉你们根本不知道谁会在这里
Almost like you didn't know who would be here.
似乎是随机的一样
Like it was random.
这似乎说不通
It doesn't make sense.
你们给到我们的每一次否定，
For every "no" you give us,
我们都会以人类的罪孽而降下灾祸
we will unleash a plague for the sins of humanity.
你们是否已有决断？
Will you make a choice?
等等，快停下
Wait, stop.
不要这么做
You don't need to do this.
你们不需要那些东西
You don't need those things.
你们说过你们不能伤害我们
You said you couldn't hurt us.
你要做什么？
What are you doing?
你要干什么？别碰她
What are you doing? Don't touch her.
别碰她！离她远点！
Don't touch her! Get off her, get off her!
离她远点！
Get off of her!
文，文
Wen, Wen.
快跑，文文
Run, Wen. Wen.
我没法
I can't.
快跑
Run.
拜托，上帝啊，放我们走吧
Please, God, just let us go.
妈的
Fuck.
我好害怕
I'm scared.
一直看着我，好吗？
Keep looking at me, okay?
你们不要TM的转移视线
Don't you fucking look away from me.
一部分人类将接受审判
A part of humanity has been judged.
无论你们信奉什么，那都不是真的
Whatever it is you're convinced of, it isn't real.
- 你们不要这样 -都不是真的
- You don't have to do this. - This isn't real.
- 预言不会…… 不！
- It's not gonna... No!
如果你想你便祈祷吧我不予置评
You can pray if you want. I won't make comment.
布鲁克斯先生和夫人吗？
Mr. and Mrs. Brooks?
是的我妻子今天没法来这里
Yes. My wife couldn't be here today.
这是她的哥哥
This is her brother.
告诉我我不是在做梦吧
Now tell me this isn't a miracle.
嗨嗨，爸爸
Hi. Hi, Daddy.
嗨，文
Hi, Wen.
- 嘿
- Hey.
- 哦～ -  哦～
- Oh. -  Oh.
艾德利安，
Adriane,
你能帮我一下吗?
can you help me out here?
- 艾德利安 - 嘿，在
- Adriane. - Hey, yeah.
帮什么？
What?
帮我把雷蒙德搬到外面
Help me take Redmond outside.
我们给他盖上毯子
We'll cover him with a blanket.
文，不好意思，但我要转频道了
Wen, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to change the channel
只是一会儿，好吗？
for a little bit, okay?
罗杰斯先生：弗雷德·罗杰斯（ Fred Rogers），美国著名儿童电视节目《罗杰斯先生的街坊四邻》的主持人，被称为“除上帝外最完美的男人”
去你妈的，"罗杰斯先生"
Go fuck yourself, Mister Rogers.
我想让你尝一块这个
I want you to try a piece of this.
我想看看到底空气炸锅能不能
I want to see whether the air fryer oven
- 让它变得松脆…… - 请观看电视
- makes it just as crispy... - Please watch the TV.
- 应该马上会有新闻 - 不跟你开玩笑，
- It should be on soon. - I'm not even gonna kid you,
我是真的想吃
I really just want this.
- 各位听到那清脆的碎裂声了吗？
-Do you hear that gorgeous crispy crunch?
- 没有比这更好的了
-Doesn't get much better than that.
嗯～
Mmm.
而且吃起来棒极了
And it tastes amazing.
美滋滋炸鸡，没"油"胖负担
Amazing fried chicken and a lot less guilt.
我们继续震中位于阿留申群岛的大地震的相关报道，
We continue with our coverage of the earthquake centered in the Aleutian Islands,
较四小时前，震动更加频繁
which struck more than four hours ago.
美国国家海啸预警中心
The U.S. National Tsunami Warning Center
也向不列颠哥伦比亚、加拿大
has issued a cautionary advisory to British Columbia,
以及超过一千英里的太平洋西北部沿海地区，包括
Canada, and more than a thousand miles of coast along the American Pacific Northwest,
西雅图和波特兰等城市发布海啸预警
including the cities of Seattle and Portland.
太平洋海啸预警中心
The Pacific Tsunami Warning Center
向夏威夷群岛发布最强海啸预警
issued its strongest warning to the islands of Hawaii.
你要给我们看的就是这个？
Is this what we're supposed to see?
……高中，商场和学院，各大校区……
...high schools, malls and colleges, campuses...
我已经向你们说明过若是你们不行决断
I explained to you what would happen
会有什么后果
as a result of you not choosing.
雷蒙德之死将降下一场灾祸
A plague will be released by Redmond's death.
你听我说
You have to listen to me.
我都记得，但这说明不了什么
I remember, but this doesn't mean anything.
- 没有关…… - 不是！
- It doesn't mean... - No!
看下去！
Just watch!
我不该大声喊叫
I know I shouldn't yell.
你们惧怕我们几个
I know you're afraid of me, of us.
请……继续看下去
Just... please watch.
…指向一阵巨浪，
...points to a sizable wave
浪高达至15到20英尺（4.5-6米），
of 15 to 20 feet in height
朝南向至夏威夷群岛
headed south towards the Hawaiian Islands.
我台收到确切消息，目前海啸已确认登陆
We do have information that the tsunami has made landfall.
据我台传回的直播影像，
Now, as you can tell from our live feed,
地处考艾岛的度假地已完成疏散工作
this resort on Kauai has already been evacuated.
我们的预警探测系统
Our early warning detection systems
为民众撤离海岸以及夏威夷群岛低洼地区
gave plenty of time to evacuate the coasts
提供了充裕的时间
and low-laying areas at the affected Hawaiian Islands.
目前暂无人员伤亡
No injuries or fatalities have been reported.
拜托至少放了艾瑞克和文
Please let Eric and Wen go at least.
艾瑞克有脑震荡
Eric has a concussion.
我留下
I'll stay.
然后我们就能好好探讨末日，或者天启，
And we can talk about doomsday, or the apocalypse,
或者任何你想探讨的21世纪的大规模灾难
or mass traumatic events of the 21st century all you want.
我不理解，这不是……
I don't understand, this isn't the...
塞布丽娜，再继续看下去
Sabrina, just keep watching.
直至我们看到预见的景象
Until we see what was shown to us.
在太平洋地区，发生第二次大地震
A second massive earthquake has struck in the Pacific,
测量震级为8.6级
registering 8.6 on the Richter scale.
震中只距离俄勒冈州海岸70英里
The epicenter is only 70 miles off the coast of Oregon
地处为卡斯卡迪亚地层潜没带
in what's called the Cascadia Subduction Zone.
此地为众多科学家长期担忧的地区，能发生灾难性地震
That's an area scientists have long feared would produce a catastrophic earthquake.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
即为此灾
There it is.
由我们引发
We did this.
真的发生了
It's really fucking happening.
天哪，上帝
Oh, Jesus, God.
…考虑到震中距离,
...and given the proximity of the epicenter,
海岸附近的人员将几乎没有时间
people on the coast are gonna have mere minutes
寻找到避难场所
to try to find shelter.
此级别的近海岸大地震引发的海啸将是巨大规模的
A tsunami triggered by a quake of this magnitude and proximity to the shoreline will be massive.
近海岸的50英尺高巨浪
I-I mean, 50-foot-high bluffs
将极具危险性
along the coast are not gonna be safe.
刚得到最新消息
And we've just gotten word.
海啸确实强袭了俄勒冈州海岸线
The tsunami has indeed hit the Oregon shoreline
并且我们得到几分钟前来自卡农海滩的影像资料
and we have footage shot minutes ago from Cannon Beach.
天呐，这就是我预见的
Holy crap, this is what I saw.
一模一样的峭壁岩石
The same jutting rocks.
我也是
Me, too.
文，
Wen,
回到你的房间去，直到我喊你出来
go to your room till I tell you to come out.
不该让她看这些
She didn't need to see this.
明早，你们可以做出艰难的，
Tomorrow morning, you can make the difficult,
无私的选择，完成献祭拯救世界……
selfless choice of sacrifice and save the world...
……或者你们可与今天一般
...or you can choose once again
让时针再次转动，逐渐接近
to let the clock move another minute closer
永夜末日
to permanent midnight.
今天剩余时间以及今晚，
For the rest of today and tonight,
我们将在合理范围内满足你们的需求
we'll tend to your needs within reason.
除此之外,
But otherwise,
我们还会让你们单独考虑……
we'll leave you be to reflect...
并互相沟通
and talk it over.
我们早说了
We told you.
你们务必相信我们
You have to believe us.
不必管我们是否相信你们的疯言疯语
It doesn't matter if we believe your craziness.
我们的回答不会改变
The answer is still the same.
这世上他人的死活与我们无关
Everyone in the world can die, as far as we're concerned.
对吧，艾瑞克？
Am I right, Eric?
艾瑞克？
Eric?
你还好吗？
You okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
就是要休息一会儿
I just need a moment.
我有个小小的惊喜
I have a little surprise
- 正等着你们 - 哇哦，惊喜
- queued up for you. - Ooh. Oh, a surprise.
- 哇，会是什么呢？ - 准备好了吗？
- Ooh, what's that gonna be? - Are you ready?
- 哇哦！
- Oh! -Oh! - Yeah!
- 我们要跟着唱吗？ -那当然啦
- Are we gonna sing along? - Yes, of course.
- 让我想想，让我想想 - 好难决定呀
- I think, I think we are. - I don't know, I don't know.
♪ 姑娘，与你相伴
♪ Girl, to be with you
♪ 是我最爱
♪ Is my favorite thing
- ♪ 吧，哒～
- ♪ Bah, dum
♪ 吧，哒～
♪ Bah, dum
♪ 迫不及待，只为见你 ♪
♪ I can't wait till I see you again ♪
高潮来喽准备！
Here we go. Ready?
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
- 嘿 - ♪ 只为与你共舞
- Hey. - ♪ Just to boogie with you
- 嘿- ♪ 耶～
- Hey. - ♪ Yeah
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ 只为与你共舞
♪ Just to boogie with you
嘿
Hey.
♪ 我想同你舞到天明 ♪
♪ I want do it till the sun comes up... ♪
- 太美了
- It's gorgeous.
除了……与主干道相距甚远
Except for the... the main road being further away
此地令人神往
than we thought, I'm officially impressed.
好吧
Okay.
- 嘿，文，过来拿你的包包 - 文？
- Hey, Wen, come get your bag. - Wen?
文，快回来
Wen, come on.
文，快来看这里的风景
Wen, come check out the view.
可比网上看到的好多了
It's better than the website.
你已经抓了几只蚱蜢了？
How many grasshoppers did you catch?
目前才抓了一只
Just one so far.
她的名字是丽芙
Her name's Liv.
那你有看到熊出没吗？
Oh. You see any bears yet?
安德鲁，别起头
Andrew, don't start.
如果我们开这种玩笑，她就不会当真了
If we joke about it, she won't take it seriously.
我们不会在外面留垃圾，没事的
We won't leave the garbage out, we'll be fine.
文，给艾瑞克爸爸看看你的大熊鬼脸
Wen, show Daddy Eric your scary bear face.
- 文，快跑……快跑
- Wen, run from... Run.
嘿，文玲，宝贝，不要接近那里
Hey, Wenling, sweetie, not too close.
码头上可能有生锈的钉子
That dock might have rusty nails.
艾瑞克，就别管什么生锈的钉子啦
Eric, come on with your rusty nails.
学会享受当下的幸福
We got so lucky with this place.
呜！
Whoo!
- 快来啦！
- Get in!
- 来呀，文！
- Come on, Wen!
- 快来！ - 哦
- Come on! - Oh.
- 呜！
- Whoo!
哇哦！
Whoa!
- 我来啦！ - 艾瑞克，来喽！
- Here I come! - Eric, come!
他要跳进来啦！
He's coming in!
哦，不是吧
Oh, come on.
稍等，一小会儿
Hold on, one second, one second.
- 呜呼！ - 跳到你右边
- Woo-hoo! - Coming right at you.
- 我来啦 -耶，耶！
- Here I come. - Yes, yes, yes!
哇，水还是有点冷
Oh. Oh, it's a cold spot.
看呀，游泳游起来
Look at you swimming.
只是稍作按压
Just applying a little pressure.
就跟你说了我是护士
Told you I'm a nurse.
你可能还不买
You may not be on board
所谓"世界末日"诸如此类的账，
with all the "end of the world" stuff yet,
但至少相信我的技术
but at least trust me on that.
没有人想要事态发展成这样
None of us wanted it to go this way.
我们需要你保持清醒的头脑
We need you in a clear state of mind.
你们还有重大的决定要完成
You've got a big decision to make.
你是不是认为我是某类宗教狂，对吧?
You think I'm some kind of religious freak, right?
换我也这样想
I would, too.
实际上，除了我祖母在我年幼时
Truth is, I haven't even been to church
逼我去过教堂，长大后就再也没去过
since my grandma forced me to go when I was little.
在那时候，我一直认为宗教的事情枯燥又无聊
I always thought religious stuff was so tired and boring
并且认为人们害怕的不过是虚无
from another time, and people were scared of shadows.
然后预示的幻象开始了
Then the visions started.
起初我也不相信它
I didn't believe it at first, either.
但最终你还是会的
But you will.
当我还是孩童时，我爸爸曾对我说,
When I was a kid, my dad used to say to me,
"抱有信仰，心有依托"
"Trust in something more than you."
它在这几天都快变成我的口头禅了
It's sort of become my mantra these past few days.
我看见幻象时便说这句话
I said it when I saw the visions.
我打造出与幻象中一致的武器时便说这句话
I said it when I built my weapon exactly the way it was shown to me.
我说了一遍又一遍
I said it over and over
当我经过来此路上的每个高速公路出口
as I passed every freeway exit on my way here.
当我走在木板路上遇见他们几个时，
I said it when I walked out onto the boardwalk
我说了这句话
and I saw the others.
我们穿着和幻象里出现的色彩一致的衣物
We were all wearing the same colors we saw in our visions.
也是在那时我才确信并不是只有我
That's when I knew I wasn't alone.
并且所有的一切……
And all of this...
……都是真的
...is real.
现在我把这句话送给你，艾瑞克，
And I'm saying it to you now, Eric,
抱有信仰，心有依托
you need to trust something more than you.
也许你并不想相信所谓预言，但我们是站在救世的一边的
You may not want to believe it, but we're all on the same side.
我以家庭为重
I'm on my family's side.
艾瑞克？
Eric?
你真的没事吗？
You really okay?
我脑袋还在嗡嗡响，但视野已经清晰多了
My head's still ringing, but my vision is clearer.
你清楚第一次地震是发生在
You know that first earthquake happened
在整整四小时前的吧，是吧？
a whole four hours ago, right?
远在他们不请自来前
Before they showed up here.
莱纳德之前就在不停看他的手表
Leonard's checked his watch a thousand times.
他们在卡各个时间节点
They've been timing all of this.
我知道的
I know.
我只是不想你……
I just don't want you to...
我不想你被他们吓到或者怎样
I don't want you to be spooked or anything.
你觉得我会信他们？
You think I believe them?
不是
No.
我只是……
No, it's just...
考虑到你脑袋受伤，
With your head and all,
我想确保你还能理性思考
I want to make sure you're thinking straight.
而我们也能免于被他们操控
Without them trying to manipulate us.
我看到他们把你单独拉过去，尝试和你沟通
They take you alone in there and try and talk to you.
我不相信他们
I don't believe them.
我尽力和他们统一思想
I'm trying to keep it together.
但不起作用
This isn't gonna work.
他们永远也不可能相信我们
They're never gonna believe us, man.
而我们自身也需要保有信仰，为何何来，
We have to believe in what we're doing,
来此何为
what our goal is here.
你看见雷蒙德的死脸了吗？
Did you see Redmond's fucking face?
太可怕了
It was just crazy.
无论说什么也要说服他们
Say whatever it is you have to say to them. Convince them.
- 文！
- Wen!
文！
Wen!
喔！
Whoa!
我恐怕规矩是任何人都不允许离开此处
I'm afraid the rule is that no one's allowed to leave.
你是准备逃跑吗，文？
Were you trying to escape, Wen?
别烦她
Leave her alone.
是我叫她这么做的
I told her to do it.
你只是吓到了，文
You're just scared, Wen.
我们都是
We all are.
你们有会要求我们再次选择的
You'll ask us to choose again.
不要信他们的话，文
Don't listen to them, Wen.
我们是被针对了
We were targeted.
我们总是在被针对我们……
We've always been targeted. We...
- 安德鲁！
- Andrew!
我就记得他很面熟
I knew I recognized him.
雷蒙德……
Redmond...
就是在酒吧的那家伙
is the guy from the bar.
什么？
What?
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
什么在酒吧的家伙？
What guy from the bar?
很多年前在波士顿一家酒吧有个男的袭击了安德鲁
Andrew was attacked by a man in a bar in Boston many years ago.
那个男的后来短暂入狱一段时间
The man went to jail for a short while.
但他的名字是奥班农啊
But his name was O'Bannon.
就是他
It's him.
他变胖了，胡子不一样了,
He's gained weight and his beard's different,
但肯定是他
but it's him.
他的名字是雷蒙德
His name was Redmond.
我们跟他也不熟，莱纳德
We don't know dick about him, Leonard.
我们初次见面还是在那木板路上
We all met him for the first time on that boardwalk.
别扯了！
Stop the bullshit!
别搞这些恶心的把戏了，
This is all some kind of sick scam
你们就是想让我们互相伤害
to get us to hurt each other.
不是这样的
That's not true.
我们确实互相不太了解
We don't know why each of us is here.
这难道是巧合？一个袭击过我并让我
It's a coincidence the man who attacked me
接受治疗数年的男的恰是你们伵的一员？
and had me in years of therapy is one of your group?
把他钱包拿过来
Go get his wallet.
看看他名字到底是不是雷蒙德
I'll show you his name isn't Redmond.
不，我们不会如此行事
No, we're not doing that.
为什么？！
Why?!
他名字是如何，无关紧要
Because it doesn't matter what his name is.
关键是我们所预见的
Okay? We all had the visions.
可这也太精准了
This has to be exact.
事关重大
Everything has to be right.
他不是在我们见面前，在消息墙上告诉这间小屋的吗？
Didn't he tell us about this cabin on the message board first?
然后我们才都有了关于小屋的幻象？
And then we all had visions of the cabin?
我也不知这……
I don't know. It...
应该是我们先有了预见
No, we had the visions first.
消息墙？
Message board?
听着，我们毋需怀疑我们为何在此的原因
Look, we're not doubting why we're here.
睡吧
Go to sleep.
太阳会照常升起，
The sun will rise,
也许是我们最后的日出
maybe for the last time for all of us.
你们胡言乱语的前提就有问题
The premise of your scam is flawed.
我是一名人权律师，莱纳德
I'm a human rights attorney, Leonard.
要不要我给你展示一下那些孩子们的照片
How about I show you photos of kids
——那些被折磨杀害的孩子，成堆躺在那里？
who have been tortured and killed, lying in piles?
你想要为人类延续寻找理由，
You want to make a case for humanity to go on,
那你不会成功的
you're gonna lose.
这是我知道的一些孩子们的照片
This is a picture of some of the kids I coach.
今年，男孩们在三岁和八岁年龄段突破了记录
This year, the boys had a record of three and eight.
女孩们，在五岁和六岁
The girls, five and six.
所以，我们也不好受
So, we're not very good.
若是你听见他们的欢声笑语，你会清楚我来此的原因
If you could hear them laugh, you'd understand why I'm here.
也许你们会睡得好些，要是能更好看到对方的话
Maybe you'd sleep better if you could see each other easier.
♪ 困阻兮我立之
♪ I got some troubles
- ♪ 光阴兮阻短之……
- ♪ But they won't last...
你喜欢吃吗？
You like it?
要是去餐馆，
Come to the restaurant,
我可以做各种各样的墨西哥玉米煎饼早餐
I can make you all kinds of breakfast burritos.
俗话说鸡蛋做得好，
They say if you can make an egg great,
样样做得好
you can do anything.
艾瑞克
Eric.
绑在我手上的绳子有些松了
My hands are a little looser.
我能到汽车后备箱就行
I just need to get to the trunk of the car.
- ♪ 未曾有犬喜我微兮
- ♪ That liked me some
♪ 未曾有友为我求兮 ♪
♪ Never had a friend or wanted one ♪
♪ 躺之徜之，笑之于日，缘于我之 ♪
♪ So I just lay back and laugh at the sun, 'cause I'm in ♪
你非常有礼貌
You're very polite.
♪ 甜——甜——甜——，蜜——蜜——蜜……♪
♪ Shoo-shoo-shoo, shoo-shoo-shoo-shoo... ♪
你是个好人
You're a good person.
- 好了 - 听我说，
- Okay. - Listen,
你们这伙人是在某种社交应用上互相认识的，是吧？
you guys met on some kind of message board, right?
你们这是得了分享性妄想
You're having a shared delusion.
这是21世纪特有的健康危机
That's a uniquely 21st-century health crisis.
我说的是真的
It is real.
你们陷在了回音室效应里，你们知道吗？
You're in an echo chamber, you know that, right?
你上了网，然后发现不知是谁和你有同样的幻景，
You got online, and you found random people
于是你们便觉得你所梦见的幻景都是真的
who had random visions and you took that as evidence.
记得在一个路易斯安那州的军事基地
Remember the guy who shot up three people
有个家伙枪杀了三人吗？
in an Army base in Louisiana?
他曾就是像你们这种线上组织的一员
He was part of an online group like yours.
他们上传视频，关于那些影子政府
They posted videos about how the shadow government
是如何追踪他们并利用思想控制武器
was stalking them and using mind control weapons
尝试摧毁他们的生活
in an attempt to destroy their lives.
我们在网上互相寻得对方
We found each other online
是因为我们都诉说了相同的幻象
because we said we had the same visions.
还记得感恩节我们做了什么吗？
Remember what you did at Thanksgiving?
于是我们才决定在木板路上相见
And then we decided to meet on the boardwalk.
当我点头时就按那样做
You're gonna do that if I nod.
好了，我们继续
Okay, let's continue.
你们被赋予选择之权
You have the opportunity to choose.
并非急于催促，
I don't mean to rush you,
但我们会迅速地询问你们作出的抉择
but we're gonna ask for your decisions very fast now.
我就直说了
I'm gonna be straight up.
下一个就轮到我了
I'm the next one to go.
我的性命全由你们决定
I'm counting on you, man.
你们，就像是我最后生的希望
You're, like, my last hope here.
艾德利安，
Adriane,
你可以马上就从这儿离开
you can walk out of here right now.
离开后，看看世界，什么都不会发生
Just walk out and see, nothing will happen.
这一切不会停止，除非你们作出选择
None of this can stop until you make a choice.
你们还不明白吗？
Don't you get that already?
你们以为我想在这儿？
You think I want to be here?
我只是一个小小的厨师
I'm just some fucking cook.
我之前没和你们讲，
I didn't tell you at first,
其实我有个儿子
but I have a son.
我不想念出他的名字，但是……
I didn't want to speak his name, but...
我在此时此刻，恳求你们做应尽之事
here I am, begging you to do what has to be done
否则，我的儿子也将死去
because if you don't, my son is gonna die.
过去那几天，我不停预见他死去
Over the last few days, I've had to watch him die
一遍又一遍
over and over and over again.
我预见我的小男孩被活活烧死
I've watched my little boy burned alive
就在我的怀中
as I held him in my arms.
万物焚尽
Everything was burning.
他的哭嚎声萦绕在我脑海中，无法散去，
I can't get the sound of his screams out of my head,
甚至是此刻也是，所以……
even right now, so...
作为一名母亲，请相信我当我告诉你们
as a mother, believe me when I tell you
一切真的会发生的时候
that this is really happening.
决定权在你们手里
And it's up to you.
你们究竟看见了什么？
What exactly did you guys see?
别和他们说话
Stop talking to him.
他不相信你们
He doesn't believe you.
我们都不相信你们
None of us believe you.
就这么耗着吧
Let your time run out.
我们是不会屈服的
We're not gonna do what you want us to do.
他的名字叫做查理
His name is Charlie.
他喜欢吃煎饼
He likes pancakes.
那便如此吧
Very well.
合上你的眼睛，捂住你的耳朵
Close your eyes and cover your ears.
你们不要这样子
You don't have to do this.
你们是得了妄想症
You guys are delusional.
你们是自杀邪教的一部分
You are part of a suicide cult.
你们觉察不出吗？
Can't you see that?
停下！
Stop!
求求啦！
Please stop this!
一部分人类将接受审判
A part of humanity has been judged.
我会将她搬至另外房间
I'll move her into the other room
如此他们便不必见到她了
so they don't have to see her.
成千上万的人类即将迈入死亡
Hundreds of thousands of people are going to die now.
我们已释放第二场灾难
We've unleashed a second plague.
胡扯
Bullshit.
塞布丽娜，请把电视打开
Sabrina, put on the TV, please.
对于新型X-9病毒的研究
There have also been new developments
目前已有新进展，
with the novel X-Nine virus,
该病毒已被证实对儿童有极高致死率
which is proving particularly fatal to children.
在十岁及以下的儿童人群中
The X-Nine virus is highly transmittable
感染X-9病毒的人数激增中
amongst children aged ten and under.
此些疫情似乎分别起始于
These outbreaks seem to be originating
世界上独立的三片地区：
in three distinct pockets of the world:
开普敦，萨福克郡，英格兰，
Cape Town, Suffolk, England,
和田纳西州，纳什维尔郊外
and outside Nashville in Tennessee.
目前已对该些地区进行封锁
Lockdowns in these areas have already begun
基于对感染者感到恐惧的
as numbers rise along with fear
健康民众数量激增
for the safety of those infected.
许多公立学校已暂停课业
Numerous public schools have been suspended
并改造作为
with some being converted
临时隔离设施
into makeshift quarantine facilities.
目前仍有希望防止病毒
While there is hope that the virus will be contained
进一步扩散蔓延至其他地区……
to the geographical pockets in question...
我好像也看到什么了，安德鲁
I think I saw something, Andrew.
…这些社区被困在封锁之中
...these communities are trapped in lockdown.
什么？
What?
你在说些什么？
What are you saying?
我感觉我看到一个人
I think I saw a person.
或一个人影
Or a figure.
把电视关了
Turn the TV off.
你在何处看见了人影？
Where'd you see a figure?
在你身后的光芒中
In the light behind you.
从那面镜子反射过来的
In the reflection in the mirror.
那时你就站在雷蒙德的身后
When you were standing behind Redmond.
就在你们要攻击他前
Right before you struck him.
艾瑞克，看着我
Eric, look at me.
你得了十分严重的脑震荡
You have a severe concussion.
她都和你说了
She even told you
你会对光线极其敏感
you would be extremely sensitive to light.
并且我们现在又处于高压之下
We're under extreme stress here.
好好听我说的每一句话
I need you to listen to the words I'm saying.
深呼吸，好吗？
Breathe in for a second, okay?
我之前读到过关于这些X-9病毒的案例
I've been reading about these X-Nine cases
都是几个月前的事了，你知道的
for months already, you know that.
它TM不是降下的灾难
It isn't a fucking plague.
它就只是个新闻报道
It's a news report.
他们来这儿之前就全都知道了
They all knew about it before they showed up here
然后故意搞得弄成是他们故事中的一部分
and knowingly made it a part of their narrative.
这个人一清早都在不停查看他的手表
And this guy has been checking his watch all morning
就跟昨天一样
just like yesterday.
- 不是这样的，安德鲁 - 你们四个都戴着表
- Come on, Andrew. - All four of you have watches.
难道，你们是不约而同地戴着表来了？不是
What, you just showed up here like that? No.
你们心里清楚你们要来的这间小屋
You knew you were coming at this particular cabin
收不到信号
where cell reception wouldn't exist.
你看到屏幕下方的横幅了吗？
Did you see the banner at the bottom of the screen?
那不是直播，而是预录制的
It isn't live. It's preprogramming.
那就是个电视节目
It's a TV show.
莱纳德，塞布丽娜
Leonard, Sabrina,
他们几个早就知道X-9之类的节目会在
all of them knew this X-Nine show would be on
- 什么时候播出 - 安德鲁，这病毒
- and at what time. - Andrew, this virus
- 会蔓延至全球 - 如果你……
- is gonna spread everywhere. - If you...
这TM就是个事先录好的节目！
It's a fucking preprogrammed show!
他们知道这个病毒节目会在这个时候播出，
They knew this virus show would be on at this time,
就像他们早在来之前就知道阿拉斯加大地震和海啸预警会发生一样
just like they knew the Alaskan earthquake
and the tsunami warning had already happened
before they showed up here.
我现在头脑清楚了
I'm clearheaded now.
永远在一起
Always together.
从现在起你们不要和他说话跟我讲就行
You don't talk to him from now on. You talk to me.
我现在想看帕丁顿熊和克洛伊！
I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now!
我想看帕丁顿熊和克洛伊！
I want to watch Paddington and Chloe!
文
Wen.
我现在想看动画片！
I want to watch a cartoon now!
- 文，好吧
- Wen, okay.
我们一起倒数五个数，我们不要
We're gonna count down from five together, and we're not
- 再大喊大叫了，好吗？ - 我现在就想看！
- gonna yell anymore, okay? - I want to watch it now!
文，五……
Wen. Five...
我现在想看帕丁顿熊和克洛伊！ - ……四……
I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now! -...four...
- 好吧，我们再来一遍 - 我想看动画片！
- Okay, let's try this again. - I want to watch a cartoon!
文，深呼吸
Wen, take a deep breath.
- 五……
- And five...
四…… - 我现在想看帕丁顿熊和克洛伊！
four... -I want to watch Paddington and Chloe now!
- 文三……
- Wen. Three...
离我家人远点，你们这群臭屌丝！ - 艾瑞克！艾瑞克！
Get away from my family, you fucking losers! -Eric! Eric!
艾瑞克！艾瑞克！拜托不要这样
Eric! Eric! Please stop. Please.
- 停下！那是我爸爸 - 人人都需要你
- Stop! That's my dad. - Everyone needs you.
不！不！我一点也不相信你！
No! No, I don't believe you!
- 艾瑞克，拜托请停下来…… - 不，不离我远点
- Eric, please. Please stop... - No. No, no. Back away from me.
不准看着我不准看着我的女儿
Don't you look at me. Don't you look at my daughter!
你不清楚你究竟在做什么！
Look, you don't understand what you're doing!
我TM就不信你话！不！ - 拜托！
I don't fucking believe you! No! -Please!
不！你的话我一句也不信！滚你妈的！
No! No, I don't believe a word you say! Fuck you!
- 安德鲁
- Andrew.
我打伤你的膝盖，只是为了不让你逃跑
I hit you in the knee just so you wouldn't run away.
这就像在急诊室给伤员验伤分类
This is triage, like in an emergency room.
我们必须有所取舍，为多数人考虑
We have to make the decision to save the most lives.
We have to help each other.
我们必须互帮互助
- 把门打开！
- Open up!
安德鲁，听我说！
Andrew, listen to me!
安德鲁
Andrew.
快快
Come on.
请！出来！
Please! Come out!
- 快快
- Come on.
离我远点
Stay away from me.
离我远点，否则我会杀了你！
Stay away from me! I will kill you!
离我远点！
Stay away from me!
请快停下来！
Please stop!
丢下任何你在找的东西，
Leave whatever you're going for,
从车里出来，回到屋里！
get out of the car and come inside!
我不想再伤害你了！
I don't want to have to hurt you!
- 回到屋里去！
- Come back inside!
马上！
Now!
我们已经没有时间来闹了！快！
We don't have time for this! Please!
安德鲁，听我说
Andrew, listen.
现在，你听着，你这臭傻逼
Now, you listen to me, you crazy fucking bitch.
你丢掉那玩意儿，然后给我退后
You drop that thing and back the fuck up.
好吧好
Okay. Okay.
- 退后！- 好，好！
- Back the fuck up! - Okay, okay!
- 继续！ - 好，好
- Keep going! - Okay, okay.
后退！
Move!
缓口气
Breathe.
停下，停下！
Stop. Stop!
糟了，妈的
Fuck. Fuck.
退后！
Stay back!
我确信你们之所以被选中
I believe you were chosen because
是因为你们家人之间的爱是如此纯洁
your family's love for each other is so pure.
我知道你已经历了很多,
I know you've been through a lot,
而人们却对你们没有那么友善
and people haven't been fair to you.
放下武器，离艾瑞克远点，
Drop the weapon and move away from Eric,
否则我就被选中来枪毙你的那个人
or I'll show you I was chosen to put a bullet in your head.
快放下，莱纳德，否则我会杀了你！
Drop it now, Leonard, or I'll kill you!
你让我们陷入劫难，安德鲁
You're dooming us all, Andrew.
你让你丈夫陷入劫难，你让你女儿陷入劫难……
You're dooming your husband, you're dooming your daughter...
我已经受够你了！
I'm done with you!
你说的一个字我都绝对不会再听！
I'm not listening to another goddamn word you say!
下一场献祭的时间已到
It's time for the next sacrifice.
你们愿意作出抉择吗？
Are you willing to make a choice?
你真是疯了
You're crazy.
我要带走的家人，然后离开
I'm taking my family, and I'm leaving.
- 安德鲁！
- Andrew!
你有股暴脾气
You have a temper.
不是让人害怕的那种，只是……
Not in a scary way, just...
确实有
It's there.
你很紧绷
You're uptight.
你能……
You can...
回回焦虑过头
suck the life out of any situation.
嘿，说好了要实事求是
Hey, we said you have to qualify things.
抱歉，你……
I'm sorry. You...
有时会焦虑过头
You suck the life out of some situations.
这我还接受
I'll accept that.
这也不是什么坏事
It's not a bad list.
我感觉大部分家长应该有比这更糟糕的品质
I think most parents would have a worse list than that.
我都不敢想象我们要这么做
I can't believe we're actually gonna do this.
我从未，
I have never,
在我生命中任一刻，
for one second of my life,
怀疑过爱你的心
ever doubted loving you.
孩子也会被耳濡目染的
The kid'll be washed in that every day.
你是怎么做到冷不丁就开始讲情话的？
How is it you can say stuff like that out of nowhere?
你们可以小点声吗？
Can you guys keep it down?
我们说得很大声吗？
Were we being loud?
吵到我和我的朋友们喝酒了
I'm trying to have a drink with my friends.
怎么，是我们说话大声的缘故？
Oh, we were being too loud?
是这样吗？
Is that what it is?
带着你烂醉的屁股回你座位
Get your drunk ass back to your seat.
操你妈
Fuck you.
你不该挑衅他们
You shouldn't provoke them.
我没挑衅……
I wasn't provoking...
我天，什么情况？
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
什么情况？安德鲁，你还好吗？
What the fuck? Andrew, are you okay?
- 安德鲁
- Andrew.
我天！什么情况！
Oh, my God! What the fuck!
快叫救护车！
Somebody call an ambulance!
安德鲁！安德鲁，看着我
Andrew! Andrew, look at me.
安德鲁，看着我你还好吗
Andrew, look at me. Are you okay?
张开眼睛张开眼睛
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
你能听到我说话吗？安德鲁！
Can you hear me? Andrew!
好了，你拿到的是型号HK P30手枪
All right, so what you got here is an HK P30.
德国工艺，很轻，好掌控
German engineered, very light, very easy to handle.
几乎适合任何场景
Um, pretty much good for any scenario.
佩戴，家中保护
Carry, home protection.
射穿他们，对吧？
Screw 'em, right?
我就要它了
I'll take it.
别，莱纳德
No, Leonard.
你们愿意作出牺牲吗？
Are you willing to make a sacrifice?
不会，你个混蛋
No more, you bastard.
一部分人类将接受审判
A part of humanity has been judged.
我们四人无法作出决定
The four of us can't make this decision.
必须是出于你们的选择
It's got to be your choice.
闭嘴吧
Shut your mouth.
盯着莱纳德
Keep an eye on Leonard.
他要是敢动就叫喊起来
Yell if he does anything.
是奥班农
It's O'Bannon.
他们是来这里折磨我们的
They were here to torture us.
我们不知我们被选择的原因
We don't know why we were chosen.
你的臭嘴别再说一个字了！
Don't say another word of your horseshit!
全都是假的，我们明显是被针对了！
None of this is real, and you were targeting us!
我总是在寻找动机，莱纳德
I always look for motive, Leonard.
比如说一个偏执狂
How about a crazy bigot
在某个酒吧遇见一个酒保，
meets a bartender from a bar somewhere,
然后他们找到了一个来自偏远小镇的女人
and they find a woman from a small town
刚好有极端的宗教信仰
who has extreme religious beliefs.
不是这样的
That's not true.
然后他们遇到一个年轻的女人
Then they come across a young woman
她什么鬼话都信
who can be persuaded of anything.
我一点也不相信艾德利安有一个孩子，莱纳德！
I didn't believe for a second that Adriane had a kid, Leonard!
我不像你们是个杀人犯，
Now, I'm not a murderer like you guys,
所以我会把你关在卫生间里
so I'm gonna lock you in that bathroom.
他们爆了我们的轮胎，
They slashed our tires,
但他们肯定是开车过来的
but they must've come in a... a truck or a vehicle.
我们得去那辆车里
We have to get to that vehicle.
你对我们的判断都是错的
You're wrong about all of us.
立刻进到那个卫生间里，莱纳德
Now get in that bathroom, Leonard.
不要怀疑，
And make no mistake,
必要情况下我会TM杀了你
I will fucking kill you if I have to.
我们需要把门把锁固定住
We need something to tie the doorknob to.
那个灯
The lamp.
给
Here.
好了，咱们走
Okay. Come on. Come on.
他打破玻璃窗了
He broke the window.
他逃出去了
He got out.
他又会来找我们的！
He's gonna come get us!
他会抢在我们之前上车
He's gonna get to the car before us.
或他会在外面伺机而动
He could be outside and hurt us.
我们必须确保他在卫生间里
We have to make sure he's in the bathroom.
莱纳德？
Leonard?
如果我开门看见你，我会对你射击
If I open this door and I see you, I will shoot you.
莱纳德！
Leonard!
放开他！
Get off him!
我天，糟糕
Fuck. Fuck.
我以为你不会杀我们的
I thought you wouldn't kill us.
我不会的
I won't.
但我可以朝你腿上射一枪
But I will shoot you in the leg
免得你们又想离开小屋
to keep you from leaving this cabin.
打开电视如果你们还想确认的话
Turn on the TV if you want to be convinced.
你会看到所有我说过的
You'll see that everything
事情都会逐一发生
I said was gonna happen has happened.
没有人会按照你说的做…… - 更多可怕的图像
No one's gonna do what you say... -More terrifying images
我们可以看到又一架航空客机
as we see yet another passenger aircraft
- 直追地面
- plummet to the ground.
- 艾瑞克，你在做什么？
- Eric, what are you doing?
为什么要把电视打开？
Why did you turn it on?
当地和国际政府
Local and international governments
正在调查此类坠毁事件之间是否有相关性
are investigating whether there's any correlation between the crashes.
我们还未从航空公司收到相关死亡人数公示与声明
We have yet to receive death tolls or receive any statements from the airlines.
你说过这不是真的
You said it wasn't real.
天幕坠沉，冲撞地面
The skies will fall and crash to the earth
犹如玻璃碴
like pieces of glass.
上帝之指将焚焦地面……
And God's fingers will scorch the earth...
永夜将至，之于人类，光明永逝
and an everlasting darkness will descend over humanity.
我们现已确认
We now have confirmation
多达700架飞机在毫无预兆的情形下坠毁
of as many as 700 airplanes having crashed without warning,
甚至没有发出求救信号
without issuing distress calls,
其中不少担忧与俱增的怀疑
amid fears and increasing speculation
可能是遭遇了有组织的网络攻击……
there may have been a coordinated cyberattack...
恐怖主义跟这次事情一点也没关系
That terrorist stuff has nothing to do with this.
这段话我已经听过
I've heard this before.
运输安全管理局尚未发表声明
TSA has yet to issue a statement.
全球机场正在取消所有航班
Airports around the globe are canceling flights.
- 此事很难……
- It is hard... - It is hard...
- 不好意思
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
实在是难以解释我们所看到的一切
It is hard to describe the images that we are seeing.
我们充满不安和恐惧
They fill us with disquietude and horror.
我们正在见证难以理解的灾难集合体
We are witnessing a collective tragedy
就在不久前
unfathomable only moments before.
我台收到关于航机的更多消息……
We are getting word of more airline...
你TM是怎么知道她要说什么的？
How the fuck did you know what she was gonna say?
这是一些闭路电视吗？你们是怎么录制进去的？
Is this some closed-circuit TV? Did you guys pump this in?
或许真相就是……
Maybe the truth is...
末日正在临近
is that the end was happening
早在我们到达这间小屋前
long before we got to this cabin.
也许我们此刻所见并不是最初绽放的烟火
And what we're seeing now isn't the fireworks.
而是收尾的闪烁火花
It's just the final flickering sparks.
我不知道到底发生了什么
I don't know what's going on here,
但你们开来的车子的钥匙在哪里？
but where are the keys to the truck you guys came in?
安德鲁
Andrew.
我要带着我的家人……我们要离开
I'm taking my family... and we're leaving.
你真的认为今天发生的一切，
Do you really think that everything that happened today,
我们看到的一切……
everything we've seen...
你真的认为都只是巧合吗？
Do you really think it's all just a coincidence?
是的
Yes.
都只是巧合
I think it's all a coincidence.
一些可怕，难解的巧合
Some horrible, unexplainable coincidence.
或者只是一个把戏
Or it has to be a trick.
我必须这样认为！
I have to believe that!
你内心已经松动了
You already don't believe that.
我看得出别人说谎
I know when someone's lying.
艾瑞克……
Eric...
我们走
let's go.
我们离开这里永远也不再回来
Let's get out of here and never come back.
不要再听莱纳德说的了
Don't listen to Leonard anymore.
现在能请各位到屋后的平台上吗？
Can everyone come out onto the back deck now?
我想在外面完成仪式最后的部分
I'd like to do this last part outside.
你拿那个要做什么，莱纳德？
What are you doing with that, Leonard?
当我离去后，你们将会数分钟来阻止一切的发生
When I'm gone, you'll only have minutes to stop everything.
否则，一切都将注定
After that, it'll be too late.
所有的孩子都会死吗？
Will all the children die?
文，我想你带着你的音乐和耳机
Wen, I want you to take your music and your headphones
去我们之前爬过的树屋那里
and go to that tree house that we climbed in.
打开你的音乐，在那等我们来找你
Put your music on until one of us comes to get you.
听爸爸的话，好吗？
Do what Daddy says, okay?
我爱你，宝别
I love you, chicken.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
去吧，去吧
Go. Go.
我们三个不会有事的
Nothing can happen to the three of us.
你不要担心
You'll be okay.
幻象中最糟糕的部分就是嘶吼声
The worst thing about the visions was the screaming.
我几乎听见所有人的尖叫嘶吼
I could hear everyone screaming.
我也知道当幻象结束时，
And I knew when the visions ended,
尖叫声，嘶吼声，不会停息
the screaming was just gonna go on and on.
你知道我教书最爱的部分吗？
You know what I loved most about teaching kids?
他们相信任何你说的
They believe everything you say.
因此你必须格外精神
So you have to be careful.
只说你知道的，你确定是真的东西
Say only what you know, what you know to be true.
十分重大的责任
It's a big responsibility.
也许我教过的其中一位孩子
Maybe one of the kids I taught
会对世界作出重大贡献
will do something great for the world.
你们说呢？
What do you think?
请……
Please...
我的新朋友，艾瑞克，安德鲁……
my new friends, Eric, Andrew...
……你们会作出抉择并拯救世界吗？
...will you make a choice and save the world?
所有人类都将接受审判
All of humanity has been judged.
我们还有一些时间的，他说过
We still have a few minutes, he said.
艾瑞克
Eric.
我在光里看到一些事情
There was something in the light.
一个人影
A figure.
我现在感受到了
And I feel it now.
我相信你
I believe you.
我们仨走吧
Let's the three of us leave.
也许它就是这样一直运作着的
Maybe this is the way it's always been.
也许一直以来有许许多多家庭也在作出这种抉择
Maybe families have been deciding this all through time.
我们那就只管向前走吧
Let's just walk the earth, then.
就我们仨
The three of us.
那对文来说是怎样的人生？
What kind of life is that for Wen?
安德鲁，这不是入室盗窃
Andrew, this wasn't a home invasion.
他们没有锁定我们
They didn't target us.
他们来这里与我们花费时间……
They came here to spend time with us...
……让我们了解他们
...for us to get to know them.
他们让我们看到了人性的各个面
They remind us of all aspects of humanity.
雷蒙德，恶意
Redmond, malice.
艾德利安，哺育
Adriane, nurturing.
塞布丽娜，治愈
Sabrina, healing.
莱纳德，指引
Leonard, guidance.
他们就是天启四骑士
They're the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse.
我相信我们不得不见证他们的死亡
I believe we had to see them die.
感受到他们的牺牲
We had to feel their loss.
为什么是我们？
Why us?
我们没什么特别之处
We're nothing special.
因为我知道当我们看到在孤儿院见到文时的感受
Because I know what I felt when we saw Wen in that orphanage
我们最初在一起时的感受
and we were together for the first time.
这是我们的抉择
It's our decision.
这是我们他们的抉择？
It's our fucking decision?
我们应该为了他们放弃我们的爱吗？
We're supposed to give up our love for them?
这就是牺牲，安德鲁
It's a sacrifice, Andrew.
我们愿意为了众生
That we would be willing to give up
愿意放弃对我们来说如此珍贵美丽的东西
something so beautiful to us for everyone else.
- 他们不值得！
- They're not worth it!
他们憎恨我们，艾瑞克
They hate us, Eric.
他们憎恨我们的存在
They hate that we exist.
- 他们只是害怕而已
- They're just scared.
就像我们都是
Like all of us.
他们都是怪物
They're monsters.
他们摧毁着一切
They destroy everything.
他们互相伤害
They hurt each other.
你可以对一切控诉
You're not just a prosecutor.
但你也深知我们所捍卫的东西
You know there's something to defend.
这是你愤怒的来源，安德鲁
That's where your anger comes from, Andrew.
杀了我
Kill me.
不，亲爱的
No, sweetheart.
我们没有时间了
We're running out of time.
也许我看见了人影，也许是我胡思乱想的
Maybe I saw a figure, maybe I just made it up,
但它给了我安宁
but it's giving me peace.
我已经能淡然面对
My mind is set in its truth.
我不会感到害怕
I won't be scared.
你必须马上行动
You gotta do it now.
没有时间了，我们所有人
We're out of time. All of us.
我不相信他们，艾瑞克
I don't believe in them, Eric.
我相信
I do.
在我还伴随着美好念头的时候动手吧
Do it while I'm thinking the most beautiful thought
如此我心中便能带着这样的美好感受离去
so that I can have that feeling in my heart to take me
无论我将去何方
right to wherever it is I'm going.
真的快到时间，我能感受到
It's almost time. I can feel it.
杀我吧，艾瑞克，拜托
Kill me, Eric, please.
拜托，拜托
Please. Please.
我畅想着我们女儿的未来
I'm thinking about our daughter in the future.
她过着与自己想法如出一辙的生活
And she's living her life exactly as she wanted to.
她做着自己的练习
She's got her own practice.
你在她身边
You're there with her.
你们在给办公室关门，
You guys are locking up her office,
因为准备去吃晚餐了
because you guys are going to dinner.
她和我们所希望的一模一样
She is everything we always hoped for.
她仍会发出她咯咯的笑声
She's still got her crazy laugh
她仍会像每个人疯狂提问
She still asks everybody questions about everything.
她找到爱她的那个人
She found someone who loves her
而她也深爱着对方
and who she loves just as much.
就像她的爸爸们一样
Just like her dads.
艾瑞克
Eric.
艾瑞克爸爸救了所有人吗？
Did Daddy Eric save everyone?
我们及时阻止了一切吗？
Did we stop it in time?
那边有一个餐厅
There's a diner over there.
我们唯一能做的就是爬出
The only thing we could do was climb out
楼上的窗外到达屋顶，但是……
of the u-upstairs window onto the roof, but...
- ……洪水一直攀升得
- ...water kept climbing
越来越高
higher and higher.
没有人能听到我们的呼救
I mean, no one could hear us.
和我的女儿们站在屋顶上，我的女儿……
Standing on the roof with my daughters, my girls...
我以为挺不过去了
I thought it was the end.
我其中两个姑娘，她们无法，不会游泳
And two of my girls, uh, they can't, they can't swim.
接着洪水突然……停止上升了
And the water just... stopped rising.
换个频道
Switch to the other one.
在澳大利亚和俄罗斯的最后几架飞机
The last of the planes in Australia and Russia
已安全着陆
have landed safely.
大量民众涌向机场
Families are rushing to airports,
寻找他们的家人
searching for their loved ones.
在这样混乱之下是动人的场景……
Amidst this chaos are emotional scenes...
我们之前把大量尸体抬进停车场
We were rolling the bodies out into the parking lot
因为没有其他地方可以安置了
because there wasn't room.
过去的一小时是这么长时间来第一次
This past hour is the first time in many, many hours
没有在ICU出现死亡病例
that we haven't had a death in the ICU.
实际上，我们马上要度过在这里无死亡病例的
Actually, we're coming up on our second hour here
第二个小时
of no deaths.
我知道
I know.
我也深爱着你
I love you so much.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
嗯
Hmm.
之前突如其来的闪电
The sudden lightning strikes
引发多地起火，目前已无踪影
that set fire to many areas have not returned.
尽管一部分火灾尚未熄灭
Though several fires have yet to be extinguished
和对于农村和城市的损害
and the damage to regions both rural and urban
在英国地区是广泛的
across Great Britain is extensive
并且有待确认，
and remains to be determined,
最严重的爆发已经，在此刻……
the worst conflagrations have, as of this moment...
♪ 姑娘，与你相伴……
♪ Girl, to be with you...
♪ 啊-哈，啊-哈
♪ Ah-ha, ah-ha
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ 只为与你共舞 ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you, yeah ♪
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋，只为与你…… ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes, just to boogie... ♪
♪ 耶
♪ Yeah
♪ 我想穿山
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ 只为与你共舞
♪ Just to boogie with you
♪ 呼
♪ Whoo
♪ 啊……耶
♪ Ah... yeah
♪ 舞起来，舞起来
♪ Boogie down, boogie down
♪ 呼
♪ Whoo
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ 只为与你共舞 ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you, yeah ♪
♪ 我想穿上
♪ I want to put on
♪ 我——的布吉鞋 ♪
♪ My, my, my, my, my boogie shoes ♪
♪ 只为与你共舞 ♪
♪ Just to boogie with you, yeah ♪
♪ 我想穿上……
♪ I want to put on...